原创翻译  双语字幕
最新连载海外影视剧下载
请登陆 www.YYeTs.com
仅供交流学习  禁止商用盈利
翻译     千只鹤飞过波千鸟  tong大梨
翻译     五天  二糯米  屯栗子
校对     屯栗子
时间轴     兜兜兜爹
后期     渔夫
总监     屯栗子
扮巴仔超人
我们最爱的辛普森一家
辛普森一家
第三十一季  第三集
别挡我的道
Come on, out of my way!
我开车去教堂的时候怎么不堵车
Where was this traffic when I was driving to church?
侯默  冷静
Homie, calm down.
我们不会错过圣卡斯特兰纳塔节
We're not going to miss the San Castellaneta Festival.
我爱圣卡斯特兰纳塔
I love San Castellaneta.
美味的食物  友好的人
Delicious food, wonderful people.
就像在意大利一样
It's just like being in Italy.
但是其街道宽得正适合我的体型
But with streets that are wide enough I can fit in them.
我喜欢危险的游戏座椅
And I love the rides that are dangerous
因为设施已经100年了
because they're 100 years old.
倾斜转椅
破伤风之塔
小马慢走
抓住老农民
几乎走不满一圈
圣卡斯特兰纳塔节
煎饼卷  通心粉  披萨  意面  冰激凌
抓紧了  孩子们  开始了
Hold on, kids. Here we go.
我赢了一头骡子和一头公牛才得到这份工作
I beat out a mule and an ox for this job.
诀窍就是别问福利
The secret is not to ask for benefits.
*给我披萨  给我通心粉*
*Give me pizza, give me pasta*
*给我好多好多煎饼卷*
*Give me lots of cannoli*
*我要喝茴香酒喝到吐*
*I'll drink sambuca till I puke-a*
*然后再吃冰激凌*
*Then I'll finish with spumoni*
*喝到两条腿摇摇晃晃*
*Drink until my legs are Jell-O*
*廉价红酒和柠檬酒*
*Cheap red wine and limoncello*
你要我们从节日上给你
You want us to bring you anything back
带点什么吗  小东
from the festival, Tone?
不用  那都是碳水
No. It's all carbs.
我不想让人觉得我很胖
I don't want people to think I'm fat.
但你的名字叫胖东尼
But your name is Fat Tony.
名字没毛病
It blends.
真不敢相信你竟然不去
I can't believe you're not going,
我都把你叔叔从西西里带过来了
after I flew out your uncle from Sicily.
-白痴  -正是因为这个冰冷的眼神
- Idiota! - That icy glare
我才离开了那个国家
is why I left the old country.
守口如瓶  你根本不能领会我的心情
Tightlips, you do a poor job of reading my moods.
但你是我唯一可以信任的人
But you're the only one I trust.
去吧  享受节日
Go. Enjoy your festival
我就坐在这里  跟叔叔交流感情
while I sit here bonding with my uncle.
你也想去节日玩吗  齐奥
Do you want to go to the festival, Zio?
我是为了火人节才来这个国家的
I came to this country for the Burning Man.
我死之前
Before I die,
我想看裸体脆皮炸鸡骑自行车
I want to see a naked crunchy chick riding a bicycle.
*每个人都有开心事*
*Everybody has a treat*
红酒
-哦也  -那是希腊语  警长
- Opa! - That's Greek, Chief.
阿卢  圣·自作聪明节是什么时候
Hey, Lou, when's the festival for Saint Know-It-All?
-我记得是十月  -根本没有这个节
- Uh, I believe it's October the... - There isn't one!
没有人喜欢自作聪明的人  蠢蛋
Nobody likes a know-it-all. Idiot.
我们有炸面饼圈  酒烩肉卷
Hey, we got a-zeppole, we got a-braciole,
腌火腿  海螺状营养糊糊
capicola, scungilli,
还有这个我不知道是啥的东东
and I don't know what the hell-a this is.
你能把它们放一起煎一下吗
Can you make it all in one thing and fry it?
我知道你想干嘛
I saw-a you coming.
这地方看着很有意思
Ooh. This place looks interesting.
老爸别去  那是一座真正的教堂
Dad, no, that's an actual church.
无麸质饮食女士们的交流会
吃  喝  投票给昆毕
欢迎大家来到这个
Welcome, everyone, to this festival
不庆祝克里斯托弗·哥伦布的节日
that does not celebrate Christopher Columbus.
再说一遍  不是哥伦布
repeat: not Columbus.
正当我们站在
As we stand here at the corner
妮娜  皮娜和圣玛利亚街的转角
of Niña and Pinta and Santa Maria,
让我们欢迎庆典的主持人
let us welcome your master of cere-spumonies,
海王本王
Aquaman himself,
杰森·莫哦哦玛
Jason Morororora.
我很荣幸今天能站在陆地上
It is an honor to be here on land today
详述有关这位伟大圣人的振奋人心的故事
to recount the inspiring story of this great saint.
-海王  -在我的左胸上签名吧
- Aquaman. - Sign my left boob.
请签在这里
海王在这里不是为了在胸上签名
Aquaman is not here for the signing of boobs.
那是另一场在万豪酒店C会议室的活动
That's a separate event at the Marriott. Conference room C.
公元250年  伊格那丢·卡斯特兰纳塔兄弟
In 250 A.D., Brother Ignatius Castellaneta
拒绝公开宣布他放弃信仰基督教
refused to recant his Christian faith.
于是罗马人砍下他的头
And so the Romans chopped off his head,
他们砍下他的手臂
they chopped off his arms,
他们砍下他的腿  和他的脚趾
they chopped off his legs, and they chopped off his toes.
他们用冻住的蛇做成的箭射他
They shot him with arrows made of frozen snakes
拔出他的眼睛  并把他的眼珠
and they pulled out his eyes and replaced them
换成了巧克力脆皮开心果
with chocolate-covered pistachios.
但是伊格那丢依然拒绝屈服
But still, Ignatius refused to recant.
所以他们用樱桃起泡酒煮了他的骨头
So they boiled his bones in sparkling cherry wine.
这就是为什么要用意大利千层冰激凌
So that's why the thrice-martyred saint
纪念这位三次殉道圣人
is remembered with spumoni,
巧克力脆皮开心果樱桃冰激凌
the chocolate pistachio cherry ice cream treat.
不好吃
Ugh. Not good.
好了  谢谢你  超级鱼
Uh, yes, uh, thank you, Super-Fish.
现在  让我们展示出对耶稣深厚的敬意
And now, let us show our deep reverence for Jesus
用美钞装饰过的耶稣的雕塑
by festooning his statue with dollar bills.
在耶稣身上贴美钞  侯默
Pin a dollar on Jesus, Homer.
他不需要钱
He doesn't need money.
我听说他爸富得流油
I hear his father's loaded.
我的钱包去哪了
Hey, where's my wallet?
我的钱包也不见了
Yeah, my wallet's gone, too.
-我的手提包  -我的腰带
- My purse! - My belt!
我的女式无带手提包
My clutch!
我们都是泛滥的偷包案的受害者
We are the victims of a pocket-picking pandemic.
做点什么  水豹[恶搞黑豹]
Do something, Wet Panther!
无名三只手真的偷了那么多钱包吗
Peter Piper picked a peck of pocket wallets?
钱包去哪了
其偷包的行为导致多少人流离失所
How many paupers did Peter's pocket picking produce?
恐怕在盯裤子狂魔面前没有一条裤子能幸免
I'm afraid no pants are safe from this Dockers stalker,
长裤强盗  翻裤子的贼
this chino bandito, this trouser browser.
但是韦警长表示  他一定解决这个谜团
But Chief Wiggum vows he will solve this pickle of a puzzle.
我已经解决了
Oh, I solved it, all right.
范围
穿蓝色制服的男性
有礼貌的小偷  有礼貌的小偷
"Thief of polite." "Thief of polite."
我先说的
I said it first!
韦根  我不想打扰你处理这么重要的警务工作
Wiggum, I hate to interrupt this important police work...
警察  哦对  警察的小偷
"Police." That's it. "Thief of police."
我得用遥控器换台到《直通好莱坞》呢
Hey! I need that to switch to Access Hollywood.
你需要的可不止如此
You need a lot more than that.
我是莱诺拉·卡特
I'm Lenora Carter,
总检察长办公室的特别调查员
special investigator from the attorney general's office,
我来接手这件案子
and I'm taking over this case.
女士  你看起来人不错
Uh, look, ma'am, you seem nice,
但是没有人能在我的辖区里对我指手画脚
but no one comes into my precinct and tells me what to do.
-闭嘴  给我听好了  -是  长官
- Shut up and listen. - Yes, ma'am.
你是我见过最差劲的警察  我还是第一次
You are the worst police officer I've ever had the pleasure
想要当着其手下的面羞辱一个人
of humiliating in front of his men.
死肥猪  你是好警察也是坏警察
You are so fat, you're good cop and bad cop.
你的搜毒犬在戒毒
Your drug-sniffing dog is in rehab.
其实是要戒性瘾
Okay, it's for sex addiction.
甜甜圈
还有你们  两个好基友
You there! Riggs and Murtaugh.
是时候干点真正的警察该干的活了
It's time to do some real police work.
我知道了  行吧  你们继续
I see, fine. No, go ahead.
我去射击场上释放一下情绪
I'll go work out my feelings on the gun range.
我们没有射击场
We don't have a gun range!
春田警察局
我们用装了定位器的钱包设下圈套
We'll trap the pickpocket by planting a wallet with a tracer
放在一个巨大的屁股里  任何罪犯都不会错过
in a rear end so huge, no criminal could miss it.
-我们要找到镇子上最大的屁股  -你们好
- We need to find the biggest ass in town. - Hello.
能告诉我去公园长椅拆除办公室的路怎么走吗
Could you direct me to the Office of Park Bench Removal?
先坐一下  先生
Yeah, just take a seat, sir.
谢谢  我自己带了座
Thank you, I have my own.
我不能让我的丈夫冒生命危险
I'm not letting my husband risk his life.
我承认  我很害怕
I admit it, I'm scared.
女士  这是关系到公众的紧急事件
Ma'am, this is a matter of public urgency.
你丈夫的臀部比咱俩加起来都大
Your husband's rear end is bigger than the both of us.
有了你孩子的允许
With your kids' permission,
就能看到你父亲用屁股把案子搞定
we can watch your father's butt crack this case wide open.
搞定
"Wide open."
侯默  我们把跟踪设备放在你的钱包里
Homer, we're placing this tracking device in your wallet.
然后你就带着这块肥美的诱饵四处乱逛就好了
Then you just have to put that sweet seat meat on the street.
让我把你的钱包往上拉一点
Now let me pull your wallet up
这样它就能刚好露出来一点
so it's just peeking over the pocket.
别别别  让我来
Uhp-bup-bup. Allow me.
选一张卡  随便选
Pick a card. Any card.
谢天谢地这个人是我们这边的
Thank God that thing is on our side.
亲吻镜头
我们锁定到目标了
We've got our target.
你在这干什么
What are you doing here?
我承认
I admit it,
我不能退出  我在跟踪你们
I couldn't stay away. I was following you.
我正好在开车兜风哄拉尔夫睡觉
Also, I was driving around to put Ralphie to sleep.
这孩子就是不肯睡觉
That kid will not go down.
我是个乐透球  你又输了  爸爸
I'm a lotto ball. You lose again, Daddy.
准备行动
We're going in.
喂喂喂  除了你
Ah-ah-ah. Except you.
与你工作了大半辈子的同事
Ah, you work with two guys all your life
你自以为了解他们
and you think you know 'em.
却被他们背叛  阿卢还有那个谁
Betrayed by Lou and, uh, the other guy.
他叫啥来着
What is his name again?
可能是葛列格
I-I want to say Greg.
叔叔  客人就像鱼  三天就发臭
You know, Uncle, guests, like fish, stink after three days.
我早告诉过你  无数次
I told you once, I told you a thousand times,
我不会离开  除非我妻子原谅我
I'm not leaving until my wife forgives me.
-她死了  -你总替她说话
- She's dead. - You always take her side!
警察  你们在这干嘛
Cops? What are you doing here?
我们被陷害了  这些是什么
This is a setup. W-What are these things?
不是说这有个快闪式亚洲风格融合餐厅
I was told this was an Asian fusion pop-up restaurant,
亚洲人在哪  也没见融合啊
but I see no Asian nor fusion.
马里昂·安东尼·达米哥
Marion "Fat Tony" D'Amico,
你将以扒窃团伙头目嫌疑人身份被逮捕
you're under arrest for heading a pickpocket ring.
但我从没见过这些钱包
But I've never seen these wallets before.
房间怎么在旋转
The-the room is spinning.
原来这就是无辜的感觉
So this is what it feels like to be innocent.
原来这就是与我无关的感觉
And this is how it feels to be irrelevant.
爸爸是大象
Daddy's an elephant.
不我不是大象  拉尔夫
No-no, I'm not an elephant, Ralphie,
你可要牢记
and-and please don't you forget it.
恶棍老老实实吃牢饭
钱包街之狼
The Wolf of Wallet Street?
大名鼎鼎的黑帮老大
Reputed mobster
胖东尼·达米哥终难逃法网恢恢
Fat Tony D'Amico is at last behind bars.
我妻子
My wife.
我情人
My goomar.
我的茶杯猪
My teacup pig.
放学接孩子区域
怎么了  警长
What's wrong, Chief?
马姬  你可曾觉得生命流逝
Marge, you ever felt like life has passed you by,
一切变得毫无意义
there's no point?
一段困难时期罢了
Oh, you're just having a rough patch.
人到五十都会有
It happens to all men in their 50s.
我三十八  马姬
I'm 38, Marge.
警长  知道我为什么爱我丈夫吗
Chief, do you know why I love my husband?
出于最浪漫的原因  惯性
For that most romantic of reasons: inertia.
我爱他的无惧失败
I love him because he's not afraid to fail.
他与生俱来的无畏对错的自信  你也值得拥有
He has boundless unjustified confidence, and you should, too.
你真这么觉得吗
Really? You think so?
我突然看到了破云而出的光芒
Boy, suddenly, I-I see a break in the clouds.
我不会让你失望的  马姬
I will not let you down, Marge.
马姬  能把我捎到车站吗
Uh, Marge, can I get a ride to the station?
拉尔夫待在车里就行
Uh, Ralphie will stay with the car.
春田监狱
耙子
明察秋毫的主  贾布罗尼斯和玛玛鲁克人
Dear Lord, who sees all, the jabronis and the mamalukes,
您知道我是无辜的
you know I am innocent.
以主仁慈  享主恩典
In your mercy and by your grace,
帮我惩罚陷害我的犹大吧
help me kneecap the rat Judas who set me up.
阿门
Amen.
万能的主  我不是个爱祷告的人
Almighty God, I'm not a praying man.
对我来说  下跪通常意味着走向不归路
For me, getting down on my knees is often a one-way trip.
我当警察是跟魔鬼做了交易
I-I know I made a deal with the devil to be chief,
但请先别管它  帮帮我  好吗
but please just ignore that and help me out, will ya?
神啊  让塑料吸管回来吧
Dear Lord, please bring back plastic straws.
纸吸管湿的太快了
The paper ones get soggy so fast.
春田监狱
按您要求  我火速
I brought the mob lawyer right away
把名帮派律师带来了  老板
like you asked, boss.
裤子都没让穿就被押过来了
They wouldn't even let me put my pants on.
差点连收费表都没拿
I was barely able to grab my rate clock.
去他妈的收费表  把我弄出去
Al diavolo rate clock. Get me out of here.
-要快  -稳住  沉住气
- And I mean fast. - Patience. Patience.
他们以什么理由逮捕你
Okay, what have they got you on?
一级谋杀
Murder one
二级谋杀
Murder two?
扒窃  别说那么慢
Pickpocketing! Quit talking slow!
好
All right.
其实我是无辜的
Actually, I'm innocent.
无辜  无辜吗
Innocent?! Innocent?!
法官根本不会信你
A judge wouldn't believe you for a second.
我无能为力了
I've got nothing to work with here.
你还请律师干嘛  就是你干的
What would you even plead? You really did it this time.
不是我干的
I didn't do it.
我要揍他吗  老板
You want me to whack him, boss?
不用了  带他出去
No! Just usher him out.
好的  我会"带他出去"
Got it. I'll "usher him out."
我是指领他出去
I mean show him the door.
对  我会"领他出去"
Right. I'll "show him the door."
不管你以为的是什么  反着做
Whatever you think I want you to do, just do the opposite!
忘记他吧
胖东尼被判二十年
春田警局
圣卡斯特兰纳塔节录像
东尼·达米哥二十三岁罕见采访
我唯一不会犯的罪行就是扒窃
The one crime I would never commit is pickpocketing.
他看起来很真诚
Huh. He seems sincere.
我就是认真的
I am sincere.
我还是小男孩时  我爸爸法斯托·安东尼奥
When I was a boy, my father, Fatso Antonio,
要做心脏移植手术
needed a heart transplant.
但是那颗心脏在路上被偷了
On its way to the hospital, that heart was pickpocketed.
没有任何伟大的男人该这样死去
My father died the way no made man should die:
竟然是自然死亡
of natural causes.
老天  我发现了一条线索
Oh, my God. I discovered a clue.
我发现了一个电动牙刷
I found an electric toothbrush.
至少他今晚能好好睡觉了
Well, he'll sleep good tonight.
我敢肯定他是无辜的
I can tell he's innocent,
就凭我曾把上百个无辜者送进监狱
with a certainty you can only develop
培养出来的直觉
putting hundreds of innocent people in jail.
韦根的错案
DNA技术总是和我作对
DNA technology has not been my friend.
春田监狱
马桶意面
熄灯了
Lights out!
嘶  嘶  嘶
Psst. Psst, psst.
干嘛偷偷摸摸的  我又不会逃跑
Why do you "Psst" Me? I'm not going anywhere.
我觉得你是无辜的
I think you're innocent.
但是你得努力说服我
But you're gonna have to convince me
无视你过去的那些恶行
to ignore your entire past history.
我并非生而富贵
I was not born a rich man.
在我的成长环境里  只有靠拳头才能生存
Where I grew up, there was one way out: your fists.
或者靠那些提供给意大利裔年轻学生的
Or the many scholarships available
大量奖学金计划
to young Italian-American students.
但是奖学金申请表上要填写个人信息
But the forms required information,
我是不会告密的
and I ain't no snitch.
我开始失去信心了
All right, I'm losing my confidence.
是你干的  对吧
You did it, didn't you?
以这位前神父的名义发誓  不是我
I swear on this former priest that I didn't do it.
他无罪
He's not guilty.
-我知道什么是有罪  -我可以证明
- And I know guilty. - And I can prove it.
-那证明呀  -我只说我可以
- Well, go ahead. - I said I can prove it.
没说我愿意
I didn't say I would.
为啥不愿意
Well, why wouldn't you?
因为我当时在做的事不是黑帮老大该做的
Because what I was actually doing at the time is something
不能被别人知道
a mob boss cannot do and let people know.
如果你配合  我对天发誓
If you help me, I swear an oath
我们会找到那个陷害你的人
we'll find the guy that framed you.
好吧  我告诉你犯罪发生时
All right, I will show you what I was doing
我正在做什么
when the heist went down.
这太难为情了  保证是真的
It's so embarrassing, it has to be true.
把你手机给我
Give me your phone.
正经商人俱乐部  监控录像
密码:不是我
我每天这个时候都这么做
This is what I do every day at that time,
刚好是犯罪发生的时间
the time of the crime.
你会看到  我走进私人办公室
As you will see, I walk into my private space,
漱口
I gargle,
然后  你自己看吧
and then, God help me, I...
*好时光和坏时光*
*Good times and bum times*
*我都见证过  亲爱的*
*I've seen them all and, my dear*
*我还在这里*
*I'm still here*
*奢华的天鹅绒*
*Plush velvet sometimes*
*或者简单的零食加啤酒*
*Sometimes just pretzels and beer*
*我依然坚守在此*
*But I'm here... *
现在你知道了  我一个人的时候爱唱金曲
Now you know. When I'm alone, I sing show tunes.
你没偷走那些钱包  你偷走了我的心
You didn't steal those wallets. You stole my heart.
快点开
Leave it on.
*十年黑道头头  饱经风霜*
*Ten years a mob boss, hits and whacks *
*收买法官市长  从不交税*
*Bought judges and mayors, and never paid tax*
停  够了
Okay, that's enough.
有些太够了
Definitely enough.
春田监狱
马桶通心粉
我们今天就能放你走
We're gonna get you out today.
谢谢你  警长
Appreciate the offer, Chief,
但是牢狱生活改变了我
but prison has changed me.
我想我该直接放弃出狱  服满刑期
Now I'm thinking I should just give up, serve out my term,
然后坐在肉店门口沐浴暖阳
then sit in the warm sun outside the butcher shop.
你不是一直都这么做吗
Isn't that what you always did?
确实  但是每过几小时
Yeah, but every few hours,
就会有人在我耳边说悄悄话
someone would whisper something into my ear,
我得决定是点头还是耸肩
then I had to decide whether to nod or shrug.
压力使我坐立难安
It was very stressful. The agita.
我以为你想找出陷害你的家伙
Uh, I thought you wanted to get the guy who put you here.
我确实想
I do.
我们会的  如果你愿意带窃听器
Well, we will, if you will wear a wire.
抱歉  这是原则问题  不行
I'm sorry, but on principle, that is something I cannot do.
再说一遍  我不能这么做
Let me repeat: something I cannot do.
好哒:)
路易吉餐厅
伟大的人
有偿杀人
晚安好梦
记得说短语来求救
Now, remember the phrase to call for help.
-什么短语  -记得说短语
- What phrase? - "Remember the phrase."
我会的  什么短语
I will. What phrase is it?
记得说短语
"Remember the phrase."
如果你告诉我我当然会记得的
I would if you would tell me what it is.
短语就是"记得说短语"
The phrase is "remember the phrase."
这是我听过的最蠢的事了
That is the dumbest thing I've ever heard.
记住  你的人生指望着我们呢
Just remember, your life depends on us.
而且拜托  别亵渎这个词
Oh, and please, no profanity.
我跟夫人会玩这个游戏
I play these for the missus
当我们  当我们感觉来了的时候
when we're, uh, we're getting in the mood.
敬胖东尼  一个神似波提切利裸体画的人
A toast to Fat Tony, a man like a Botticelli nude
只不过又胖  又老  容易陷害  是吧
fat, old and easy to frame, huh?
大家好
Hello, fellas.
胖东尼  我只是在表达对你的思念
Fat Tony. I was just saying how much we missed you.
对吧  对吧  各位
Huh? Huh, guys?
-当然了  -我们这么说过
- Oh, yeah, sure. - Yeah, we said that.
安静  我不想听见任何人的声音
Quiet! I don't want to hear anybody
除了告密者弗兰基
but Frankie the Squealer.
你你你想...你想从我这里听到什么
W-W-What do, w-what do you want to hear from me?
那个陷害你的人的名字吗  我绝对不说
The name of the man who framed you? I would never.
我没说过是强尼·守口如瓶
I didn't say Johnny Tightlips.
我绝对不会说是强尼·守口如瓶
I would never say Johnny Tightlips.
各位  我们的新老大  强尼·守口如瓶
Ladies and gentlemen, our new boss, Johnny Tightlips.
原来是你  强尼
So, it was you, Johnny.
-什么  喂  -你
- What? Hey! Whoa! - You!
虽然你给的都是消极的回复
After all your passive-aggressive replies
和一脸不高兴表情  我却绝想不到是你
and bitter looks, I never would've guessed.
你把我沉默寡言的天性误认为是忠诚
You mistook my taciturn nature for fealty.
但那仅仅是因为在社交氛围中
But it was simply that I didn't feel comfortable
我感到很不舒服
in social situations.
之后我看到这样一个广告
Then I saw this commercial
一朵悲伤的云去跟太阳约会
where a sad cloud goes on a date with the sun.
之后我去跟我的医生聊帕罗西汀的事
So I talked to my doctor about Paxil,
这种药给了我信心去背叛你
and it gave me the confidence to betray you.
现在这是我的团伙了
This is my crew now.
对吧  吉米·拍马溜须
Ain't that right, Jimmy Kissass?
您一直是我的最爱
You was always my favorite.
你呢  桑尼·人云亦云
What about you, Sonny Go-along?
其他人都同意那我没意见
I'm good if everyone else is.
-你呢  威利·怎么都行  -怎么都行
- Willie Whatever? - Whatever.
还有你呢  乔伊·不读空气
And you, Joey Can't-Read-the-Room?
你疯了  没人会同意的
You're nuts! Ain't none of us gonna go along with this!
是的  你看  那个...你没...不是
Yeah, see, that's-- you didn't-- that's not...
*一个普通的小镇女孩*
*Just a small town girl*
我很惊讶阿麦居然不在
I'm surprised Maggie isn't here.
*孤独世界*
*Lonely world*
*她坐上了午夜火车*
*She took the midnight train*
*要去哪里*
*Going anywhere*
这份意面太好吃了
Mmm, this pasta's delicious.
我得了解一下是什么酱汁
I'm gonna find out what the sauce is.
记得说短语
Remember the phrase.
说什么短语
Remember what phrase?
对了
Oh, right.
酱汁
Ooh, sauce.
天哪  我中枪了
Oh! I'm hit!
正中菊花...中心
Right in the heart... of your ass.
得有人给我把子弹吸出来
Someone's got to suck out the bullet.
韦根  该死  这是你生来就该做的
Wiggum, damn it, this is what you were born to do.
*别停*
*Don't stop*
他醒了
There he is.
有一瞬间我们以为失去你了  冠军
We thought we were gonna lose you for a minute there, champ.
你得谢谢警长
You have the chief here to thank.
他的极速吮吸可能救了你一命
His quick suction may have saved your life.
谢谢
Thank you.
春田镇警局
韦根  我不得不说  第一次见到你时
Well, Wiggum, I have to say, when I first met you,
我觉得你非常无能
I thought you were totally incompetent.
然后呢
And?
然后然后然后呢
And?! A-And?! And?!
我相信你  警长
I believe in you, Chief.
是的  没错  这就够了
And, yeah, that-that's enough.
朱塞佩家
肉市场  提供意大利熟食
我们三个  没有那么不相同
The three of us. We are not that different.
嘿
Whoa! Hey, whoa!
那个人在说什么
What's this guy talking about?
我们是意大利肥仔
We are cicciobomba,
喜欢坐在太阳下  享受意大利熏火腿
who like to sit in the sun and enjoy a nice prosciutto.
意大利肥仔  意大利熏火腿
Cicciobomba, prosciutto.
你们的语言连垃圾话都能说得很美
You guys make garbage sound good.
我们把垃圾叫斯巴特杜拉
We call garbage spazzatura.
垃圾
Mmm... garbage.
垃圾们
Garbage.